pcspeedmaximizer.com 2011-11-09

# about us

## Privacy Policy 

Are you concerned about your privacy? Doing business together requires some sharing of information. Set out below is our Privacy Policy, explaining what information we collect and why, what we do with it and how we protect you.

## What information we collect and why

**Registration, download and purchase**   
To access certain areas of the Avanquest.com website (especially to download or to buy), you will first be asked to complete a form to either download a trial version, a free software title, or to create an account before buying any of our products.

**Registration**   
During registration, you may be required to provide your contact information, such as your name, email address, postal address, payment information and to choose a password.   
Your email addresse is your username. We send all new registered visitors and clients a welcoming email to verify their password and username.   
It’s very important that you submit a working email address because that that is where we’ll send your purchase confirmation, download links, activation keys, support and product notices. When an email address is not working, the associated password might be deactivated by Avanquest.

**Purchase**   
When buying a product on the site, you will be asked for your contact details and billing and shipping information. This data will be used to process the order, to get the payment through the credit card verification process, and to ship the item(s) you ordered. If there is a problem with the order, an Avanquest representative may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. A confirmation email is sent for each purchase to the address you give us - so if you have a few addresses take a moment to remember which one you give us.

**Download**   
When downloading a trial version or a free software program, you will be asked for contact information, including your email address. You will receive email messages related to this transaction such as to provide you with download links, activation keys, support notices and upgrades for the software. 

**Surveys and contests  
**From time to time, we request information from Avanquest.com users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary. This information is mainly used to better understand our audience and to send prizes to the winners when needed. Should the results of a contest or a survey be published, no personal information will be divulged without the explicit consent of the winners.

**“Send to a Friend” Service.  
**To use our “Send to a friend” services, you are requested to provide additional names and email addresses. For these “Send to a friend” services, Avanquest.com sends an email on your behalf containing links to the information you have selected on the Avanquest.com website – and only in that specific context. None of these email addresses are reused later, unless their owner subscribes by themselves to our services. **  
**

## What we do with it

**Your subscription to Avanquest News and Special Offers**   
When submitting your email address, you are given the opportunity to "opt-in" to the Avanquest newsletter.  By opting to receive this communication, Avanquest will send you regular emails containing relevant product and service information, new product and upgrade information, and any special offers that we think may be relevant to you.

**If you wish to unsubscribe from the newsletter  
**If at any time you wish to opt-out from these communications, please follow the unsubscribe link contained in the emails, or [email us](mailto:unsubscribe@avanquest.com "Unsubscribe") with your request to be removed from our mailing list.   
When you officially “unsubscribe” through our links or site we commit to remove the email address from our mailing lists as soon as possible, and usually before the next mailing. From that point you will no longer receive our newsletters or special offers. However, please take note that if you purchased software or downloaded trial versions in the past or if you decide to purchase or download a trial version again after you’ve unsubscribed, we may still send you service emails directly related to these transactions, such as order confirmations, product notices, expiry notifications, bug fix notifications, security alerts, compatibility notifications, or enhancements.

**No sharing of information to preserve your privacy**   
Avanquest Software is the sole owner of information collected on its websites. We will not sell, disclose, or rent this information to others except if required to by contract or through a legal proceeding or law.   
We may share aggregated information with our partners and advertisers. However, this information is not linked to any personally identifiable information. Avanquest carefully review the privacy policies of partners, affiliates and subsidiaries to ensure that they reflect the same attention and commitment to privacy as Avanquest.com

**When visiting other websites, you’re on your own.  
**Our website may contain links to other websites which are outside our control and are not covered by this Privacy Policy. If you access other sites using the links provided, the operators of these sites may collect information from you which will be used by them in accordance with their privacy policy, which may differ from ours.

**Using cookies for statistical and analytical purposes – ultimately, it’s all about improving your experience on our site.  
**Avanquest.com website uses cookies. Cookies are small pieces of information sent by a web server to a web browser, which enables the server to collect information from the browser.

The Avanquest website does not collect any personal information from cookies.  They are used to make the login process easier for our users, to allow the website to track which products you have added to your basket and your preferred country, language and currency, and to track broad user movements for statistical purposes.

Visual Sciences, provider of HBX, our web statistics service, also uses cookies to collect information from our visitors. Visual Sciences has absolutely no access to any personal information from the users. Click [here](http://www.websidestory.com/privacy/overview.html "Visual Sciences / WebSideStory") to review their privacy policy.

**If you need to correct or update your personal information**   
We provide a way to correct or update user personal data from our records should information change. If you no longer want to be on our mailing list, see our opt-out process above.   
A delay of a few weeks applies to corrections and updates of personal information as Avanquest attempts to verify the identity of a user requesting such changes to their information before they are made.   
To correct or update personal information, [send an email](mailto:salesadvice@avanquest.com "Customer Service") to our Customer Service Department or send a letter to:   
Avanquest Software - Customer Service     
23801 Calabasas Rd. Suite 2005   
Calabasas, CA 91320- USA

**And, of course, your access right**   
You have a right to access the personal data that is held about you. To obtain a copy of the personal information Avanquest holds about you, please write to us at the same address:   
Avanquest Software - Customer Service     
23801 Calabasas Rd. Suite 2005   
Calabasas, CA 91320- USA

**Notification of changes**   
You will always be warned should we modify this Privacy Policy so that you can continue to be confident about your privacy. This Privacy Policy was last updated on September 27, 2007. When we change our Privacy Policy, we will post a message on our homepage to that effect with a link to the revised Policy. In this way, you will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under which circumstances we may disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify you by way of email and you will be given a choice as to whether or not Avanquest Software may use their information in this different manner.

**Any questions?** If you have any enquiries regarding this Privacy Policy, don’t hesitate to [contact us by email](mailto:salesadvice@avanquest.com "Customer Service").
